>> Jem Young: 说到升级，现在让我们进入升级节点，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And speaking of upgrade,
let's go into upgrading node now,
缺省安装为节点 8。
the default installation is node eight.
据我所知没有任何重要的安全更新
I wouldn't say there's any major
security updates as far as I know,
可能会有 10个节点进入节点
there might be to move into node ten.
但是，让我们来做一下，因为语法比较好一点。
But let's just do it because
the syntax a little better.
MPM 是较新版本的节点的少量清除程序。
MPM is a little bit cleaner
on the newer version of node.
要这样做我们要用这个叫宵禁的命令
And to do this,
we're gonna use this command called curl,
对于客户机 URL 很短。
which is short for client URL.
这可能是你见过的命令
It's probably a command you've seen for
and
它是一个比较常见的读取和写入外部资源的命令。
it's one of the more common commands for
just reading and writing external sources.
在这种情况下，因为我们昨天做应用安装的时候，
And in this case,
because when we did app install yesterday,
我们要用什么应用回购协议
we had to use whatever
the app repo is using,
它始终是较旧版本的节点，我们想升级该版本。
which is always an older version of node,
and we wanna upgrade that.
所以我们会直接连接到 Node Source Debian repo
So we're actually gonna connect directly
to Node Source, the Debian repo,
Debian 是 Linux 的一个特点，它维护这些包。
and Debian is a flavor of Linux
that maintains these packages.
我们在做什么，我想我把它放在这里的笔记里，我做了。
What we're doing, and
I think I put it in the notes here, I did.
如果你好奇我们在做什么
And if you're curious about what
we're doing most of the time,
我要用这个叫 Explainshell的东西
I'm gonna use this thing
called Explainshell.
我在用咒骂
And I'm using curl.
这是我最喜欢的工具之一
And this is one of my favorite tools,
记得我说男人的页面是什么样子的时候就会有一些知识
cuz remember when I said man pages
are kind of like, here's some knowledge.
Explainshell 执行的操作更简单。
Explainshell does it much simpler.
所以如果你想看那个男人的网页
So if you're trying to look at
the man page for what curl-sl does,
是一种不透明的
it's kind of opaque.
但是用 Explainshell ，我们知道它是无声的，
But using Explainshell, it's really
helpful that we know that it's silent and
它就会跑了
it's just going to run.
L 表示会检查 HTTP 是否可用。
The L means it's gonna check
the HTTP is available.
而 O 表示它会输出到一个文件里
And the O means it's
gonna output to a file.
>> Jem Young: 因为我懒，嗯?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Because I am lazy, hm?
>> 扬声器 2: [INAUDIBLE] >> Jem Young: 您将看到文件输出。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: You will see a file output.
速度很快就在第二天内
It's pretty fast, within a second so.
>> Jem Young: 如果您执行 ls ，那么会看到节点源设置。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And if you do an ls,
you'll see a node source setup.
其实我要去掉那个测试日志
Actually I'm gonna remove that test log.
>> Jem Young: 如果你想看的话，一般情况下，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And if you wanna take a look
at it, which, generally if you're running
在因特网上下载脚本，这是一个安全的站点。
downloading scripts on the Internet,
this is a safe site.
众所周知， repo的维护不存在太多的安全问题。
It's well known, the repo's maintained,
it doesn't have too many security issues.
但是一般情况下，您要小心下载运行的脚本
But generally, you wanna be careful
about downloading running scripts on
因为你不知道自己在做什么
the Internet because you
don't know what it's doing.
但让我们来看一看那剧本在做什么。
But let's take a look at
what that script is doing.
而且很多
And it's a lot,
我只是向你展示因为我无法完成所有这些
I'm just showing you this just because
I couldn't go through all of it.
但我相信 Debian repo 和
But I do trust the Debian repo and
我知道这是安装最新版本的节点的已知方法。
I know that this is a known way of
installing the latest version of node.
但一般来说，如果有人给你一个脚本在你的服务器上运行，
But in general, if someone gives
you a script to run on your server,
别这么做 [ LAUGH]
don't do it [LAUGH].
没有什么好理由去做
There's no good reason to do it.
我们只是把这个作为一个巴什的剧本
And we're just gonna run
this as a bash script.
所以我们刚刚创建的那个文件
So sudo bash that file we just created.
>> Jem Young: Clear sudo bash.
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Clear sudo bash.
>> Jem Young: 那脚本在做什么，实际上不是下载节点，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And what that script is
doing, it's not actually downloading node,
只是将应用程序指针设置为不同源的节点。
it's just setting the apps pointer
to nodejs to a different source.
所以说，嘿，我要下载节点。
So it's saying, hey,
I want to download nodejs.
这里有一个更新版本的版本，只是其中的一点。
Here's a newer version of it and
just point to that.
现在我们可以说 sudo 适合安装节点。
So now we can say sudo apt install nodejs.
是的
And yes.
>> Jem Young: Nice，现在当我执行节点时 --版本，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Nice, so
now when I do node --version,
看到我在 10 号节点而不是节点 8 上
see I'm on node 10 rather than node 8,
a little friendlier.
如果你想知道， Gem，节点 11 和 12 ，我们为什么不使用这些呢 ?
And if you're wondering, Gem, node 11 and
12 are out, why aren't we using those?
我想 12 个了
I think 12 is out.
10 是 LTS 版本，你还记得我们之前谈到的 LTS，
10 is the LTS version, and
you remember earlier we talked about LTS,
这意味着长期的支持
which means long-term support.
将维护节点 10 ，即安全升级，
Node 10 will be maintained,
that means security upgrades,
固定零天，将小虫子固定到 2021年。
fixing zero days,
fixing minor bugs until 2021.
这就是为什么我们使用 LTS 版本与现代的裁剪边缘版本相比
That's why we use the LTS version versus
the modern cutting edge version is
可能有更多的虫子还没被发现
probably gonna have more bugs
that haven't been discovered yet.
也许有些安全问题我们不知道
Maybe some security
exploits we don't know.
所以，一般来说，如果我们讨论的是服务器，那么运行 LTS。
So we generally, if we're talking
about servers, run the LTS.
您的个人服务器，运行您想要的任何版本的节点，
Your personal server,
you run whatever version of node you want,
任何让你开心的事
whatever makes you happy.
你想用 08 和所有这些好东西
You want to use asynch 08 and
all that good stuff,
运行最新版本的节点。
run the latest version of node.
>> Jem Young: 我们可以更新过期的套餐。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
we can update our outdated packages.
我们现在只有一个，那就是 npm2。
We only have one right now and
that was npm2.
所以我们不需要更新它，我们昨天刚刚安装了它。
So we don't actually have to update it
cuz we just installed it yesterday.
但是，如果您想要，可以运行 sudo npm 更新 -g。
But if you wanted to,
you can run sudo npm update -g.
这将更新所有全局包。
That'll update all your global packages.
这包括关于安全的章节。
And that covers the section on security.
我们花了很长时间
We spent a long time on it.
但我们谈到了一些不保护你的申请的后果。
But we talked about some the consequences
of not securing your application.
我们讨论了防火墙和控制端口
We talked about firewalls,
and controlling ports, and
使用最少许可权许可权来控制文件许可权。
controlling file permissions using the
least permissive permissions as possible.
我们还说过要把你的申请保持到目前为止
And we talked about just keeping your
application up to date to prevent
漏洞。
vulnerabilities.